Taylor, Mildred Frick; Papers apap280
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Taylor, Mildred Frick Papers
1921-1974
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Taylor, Mildred Frick
apap280
11.4 cubic ft.
Mildred F. Taylor was a Republican politican from Lyons, Wayne County, New York. Taylor was a delegate to the Republican National Convention from New York in 1940, 1948, 1952 (alternate),and 1960; the chairman of the Wayne County Republican Committee, 1943-1956; and a member of the Assembly of the New York State Legislature, 1946-1960. This collection documents her vast political experiences, including her work on the Joint Lesiglative Committee on Historic Sites.
Collection X
Biogtaphical Sketch
Mildred Frick Taylor was born in Lyons, New York. She attended public school and graduated from the Rochester Business Institiute. Taylor was a prominent Republican member of the Assembly of the New York State Legislature between the years 1946-1960. As a member of the Assembly, Taylor was the first woman to serve on the Ways and Means Committee. Taylor also sat on the Standing Comittee on the Affairs of Villages, and the Joint Committee on Historic Sites.
Taylor was a delegate to several New York State Republican Conventions beginning in 1938 and later attended several National Republican Conventions beginning in 1940. Taylor was also extremly active in local politics in Wayne County, New York and served as the chairman of the Wayne County Republican Committee from 1943-1956. She was the first woman elected a Republican county chairperson in New York State.
Taylor's interests included the preservation of historic sites, the creation of the New York State Thruway, and the designation of the "Rose" as the offical flower of the United States. She was an active member of the Republican Party and a member of the National Order of Women Legislators, the D.A.R., the Business and Professional Women's Clubs, and the Order of the Eastern Star.
Taylor died in 1981 at the age of 75. Her husband Paul predeceased her in 1969.
Scope and Contents
The Mildred F. Taylor Papers include correspondence between members of the Assembly of the New York State Legislature, prominent members of the Republican Party, constituents, and members of historical societies; bills introduced to the Ways and Means Committee; documents on New York State history; the preservation of historical sites; brouchures from various museums; and statistics and voter registrations from the Wayne County Repbulican Committee. Also included are maps and blueprints of various historic sites and projects that Taylor worked on.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged alphabetically for each series.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Mildred Taylor donated all items, except documents on New York State history, to Syracuse University Library in 1967. Taylor donated the items on New York State History in 1978. All items were transfered to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2006.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Public Servants; Politics and Politicians; Taylor, Mildred Frick; New York (State). Legislature. Senate; Republican Party (N.Y.); New York (State). Legislature. Joint Legislative Committee on Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites; Historic preservation--New York (State); Political Campaigns—New York (State); Correspondence.; Bills (legislative records); Files by subject; Maps.
- Correspondence, 1938-1960; 3.0 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Mildered Taylor's correspondence with her constiuents, co-workers, and and other public officers. Taylor often corresponded with her constiuents about possible taxes, including a soft drink tax (1951-1952), as well as possible legislation, and news about projects that she was working on. Taylor also corresponded with her coworkers and other public officals about projects including her involvement in the creation of the New York State Thruway. Taylor also corresponded about specific New York county issues including school districts, taxes, and fire departments.
  - A.N. Christy - Correspondence, 1950; 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assembly Statistics - Wayne County, 1940; 1950; 1954; 1956; 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barge Canal - Lock Operations, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barge Canal Transfer, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Barge Canal Transfer to the Federal Government (1 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barge Canal Transfer to the Federal Government (2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biggs Memorial Papers, 1949; 1951; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Butler Conquest Road, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Business Tax, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Carlino's Conference, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clara M. Fisher - Reed Case, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Closing Letters, 1954; 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clyde, NY, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Clyde Village - Boundaries and Other Complaints, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Modern Courts, 1956; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Committee Mailing Lists and Newsletters, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Vacancy, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - County Committee Correspondence, 1950; 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - County Home and Jail, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Department of Public Works Projects - State Roads, 1958-1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District Attorney - Joseph A. Haney, 1954; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dulles Campaign (1 of 2), 1949; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dulles Campaign (2 of 2), 1949; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Erwin Road Program, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ezra Hiet and Muskrats, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Federal School District, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Food Processing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 3), 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 3), 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence (3 of 3), 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Gladys L. Hitchcock, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hermann M. Bliss Memorial Transfer Controversy, 1955-1956; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hollinger Bill - Water Controversy, 1949-1950; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Home Bureau Updates, 1949-1951; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hon. Justin Morgan, 1956; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Housing and Multiple Dwelling, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Increased Salaries for Justice, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Investigation of the Department of Education, 1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - John Taber - Congressman Correspondence, 1943-1945; 1948 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Leach and Rapid Crossing, 1951; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Letters and Newsletters - P.H. Bradley, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Constituents, 1949; 1952; 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Marion and Palmyra Road, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Marion, Dr. Allen, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Migrant, Food, and Food Processing Labor (1 of 3), 1948; 1952; 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Migrant, Food, and Food Processing Labor (2 of 3), 1948; 1952; 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Migrant, Food, and Food Processing Labor (3 of 3), 1948; 1952; 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Migrant Labor, 1956; 1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mildred Taylor Campaign, 1958; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Mis. Legislation, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Monroe - Apple, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mt. McGregor - Oxford Home, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - National Order - Women Legislation (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - National Order - Women Legislation (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - National Order of Women Legislation Convention Washington, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Newark - Arcadia Voting Districts, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Newark Interchange, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Newark Hospital, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - New School - Lyons, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - New York State Young Republican Association (1 of 2), 1932-1939 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - New York State Young Republican Association (1 of 2), 1932-1939 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New York State Young Republican Association - National Association Contacts (1 of 2), 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New York State Young Republican Association - National Association Contacts (2 of 2), 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - News Letters Record, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - North Rose School District Plight, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Northeastern Water Commission, 1950-1951; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Fall Out (1 of 2), 1959-1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Nuclear Fall Out (2 of 2), 1959-1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - NYS Agriculture Businessmen's Council, 1950; 1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Overhead Crossing - Lyons - Leach Road, 1945-1951; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - O.W.L. Correspondence (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - O.W.L. Correspondence (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Palmyra Railway Express Office, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Palmyra Village Parking, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - People Against Increased Taxes (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - People Against Increased Taxes (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - People For Increased Taxes, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Practices and Procedures, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Prior Service - Milmore, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Probation - Reynolds Case, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Public Health Law - Qualifications For Wayne County, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Public Service Commission, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ralph S. Smith, 1954; 1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Road Improvement - Atlantic Avenue Extension, 1938; 1945-1946; 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Savannah School - Meeting in Albany, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Soft Drink Tax (1 of 2), 1951-1952; 1958; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Soft Drink Tax (2 of 2), 1951-1952; 1959; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Special Session, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State Appeals, 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State Traffic Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ten Hagen Highway, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Time Off for Voting, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Thruway Toll, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Tractor Bill, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Travel Correspondence - Historical Sites Commission, 1951-1952; 1957; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Village Doctors, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Village of Lyons, 1939; 1945; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Village of Savannah, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Walworth - Penfield Intersection, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Water Pollution, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Water Resources (Van Lare), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wayne County Campaign, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wayne County Cemeteries, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Wayne County Enrollment Figures, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County Issues, 1949; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County - Local Assistance, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Wayne County Park, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County Republican Committee - Judge Persons, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wayne County Statistics, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - William Schlee, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - William A. Specht, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Young Republican Association, 1938-1940; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Bills, 1942-1965; 2.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains bills that Taylor and other members of the Assembly of the New York State Legislature sponsored. Taylor's most notable bill was the Rose Resolution #106 which she helped introduce to the Assembly in 1954. The bill passed in 1955, making the Rose the national flower of the United States. Taylor, who was the first woman to be named to sit on the Ways and Means Committee in 1953, introduced bills on education law, city tax on gross income, and even a bill that looked at the Trinity Church's coportation power in New York City.
  - Admission Fees, 1958; 1960-1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture Bills, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture and Markets Furnishing Care for Children, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amend City Tax on Gross Income - Sen. Griffith - Bill #1751, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annexation of Territory, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Discrimination on Public Housing, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bingo Law, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Black River Canal, 1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Blanket Accident Insurance - Firemen, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Education - Nomination of Candidates, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Building Code Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Building Quota Bill, 1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Building Quota Bill, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Calendar of Bills, 1959 March 24-25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cemetery Bill, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cemetery Bill, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cemetery Bill - "General Municipal Law", 1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cemetery Bill - Town Laws, 1955; 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Centralize School District, 1959 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chauffer's Bill, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chauffer's License Bill, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Checklists, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Child Care Act, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Civil Defense Bill, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Civil Defense Director Costs, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Civil Service - Added Increment, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Civil Service Bill, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Civil Service Grades, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Claims Bill, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clyde Legislation - Storm Damage, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Concurrent Resolution - Joint Legislative Committee to Recodify Village Law, 1958; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Conveyance of Cemetery Land, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - County Judges - Increase in Salary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - County Law Bill, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Crew Leader Bill, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Duties of Fire Officers, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Education Bill, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Education Bill - Galen School, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Education Bill Recodified, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Education Law, 1950; 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Education Law - Election Hours, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Education Law - Lyons, NY, 1952-1953; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Education Law - State Aid, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Election Inspectors, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Election Law Inspectors, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Election Law - Time, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Election Law - Voting Machines, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Emergency Defense Bill, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Engineer Bill, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Farm Labor, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Farm Labor Contractors, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Firemen Civil Service, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Firemen Legislation, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Firemen - Municipal Law Bill, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Firemen - Workmen's Compensation, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Fort Hunter Bill, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Four Hundred Ninety Four Amendment, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Hairdressing and Cosmetology, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Highway Machinery, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Highway - Rental Rates, 1954 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Historic Marker Bill, 1958; 1960-1961; Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Historic Places Fees, Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Housing Bill, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Inspections of Elections, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Japanese Beetle, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Judiciary Law, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jury Bills, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Jury Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jury Mileage, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Kings Farm and Garden" - Devoe/Edward's Estate/Trinity Church, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Labor Camps - Health, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lake Ontario, 1951 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Operation - Appropriation, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lewis County, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Litterbug Bull, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Membership Corporations, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Motor Boats, 1959 February 17 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Motor Vehicle or Motor Cycle Punishment, 1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Municipal Law - Awarding Contracts, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Municipal Police Training, 1959 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Musk Rats - Conservation Law (1 of 2), 1954-1955; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Musk Rats - Conservation Law (2 of 2), 1954-1955; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Netting Bill - Ontario Lake, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - New Article 6 of Construction - Statewide Court System, 1959 January 28 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Newark Village Sewers, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Nursery Bill, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Oswald D. Heck Legislative Office Building, 1960 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Physiotherapy Law, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Police Speedometers (Stiles), 1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Prior Service - NYS Teacher Retirement System, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Public Health Law Revision, 1965 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Purchasing and Selling Water, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Recording of Investments, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Red-Banded Leaf Roller - Cornell University, 1960; Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Rental Rates for Highway Equipment, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Retirement at 55, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Retirement - Social Security, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Review Assessments of Real Property, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Roadside Park - Black River Canal, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Rose Resolution, 1955; 1956; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Rubbish Containers, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Safety Belts, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - School Aid, 1955; 1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - State Aid Bill, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - State Aid - Building Quota, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - State Aid for Highways, 1960 February 02 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - State Defense Emergency Act, 1957; 1960 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - State Defense Emergency Act, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - State Commission Survey Bill, 1957; Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - State Employees - Extra Increment, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - State Employees Salaries, 1952 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - State Employees Salaries Increments, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - State Employees Withdrawal from Pension System, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Storm Damage Costs, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Superannuation Retirement of Teachers - Bill #306 and #2850, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Town and Village Committee, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Law - Unlicensed Drivers, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Village Law, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Village Law - Admission of Residents, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Village Law - Committee on Local Finance, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Village Law - Contracts for Fire Protection, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Village Law - Employment of Attorneys, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Village Law - Recodification, 1960; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Village of Newark - Land Exchange, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Village of Palmyra, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Village of Palmyra Charter, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Village Parking, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Villages - Local Improvements, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer Firemen - Benefits, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Volunteer Firemen Legislation, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Voluntary Withdrawal Retirement, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County Bills, 1954; 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wayne County - Fees of Country Clerk, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wayne County Insurance Plan, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Williamson Water District, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Subject Files, 1921-1974; 1.8 cubic ft.
  This series contains subject files that relate to Taylor's time on the Wayne County Republican Committee, as well as her relationship with the Republican Party. This series contains Wayne County Republican Committee Meeting Minutes, as well as financial records related to Wayne County and New York state. This series also contains campagin announcements and memorabilia from political campagins including the campagin of President Eisenhower. This series also consists of maps of the Erie Canal, Wayne County, and the New York State Thruway. More information about the creation of the New York State Thruway can also be found in this series. This series also includes twenty-four blue prints from 1949 that outline the State of New York's Department of Public Works plans for constructing the elimintation of the West Shore Railroad Company and the New York Central Railroad Company Grade Crossing in Wayne County.
  - 350th Anniversary - Hudson River and Lake Champlain, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Association for State and Local History - Award, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report of State Veteran Counselor Division of Veterans' Affairs Assigned to Wayne County, NY, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Assembly Adjourns to Respect Henry V. Wilson, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General Reports, 1966; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Background on Constitutional and Legal Provisions for Settling Legislators' Salaries, 1961 April 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Finances - State Assembly Woman, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Charles Brasser - Appointment to Supreme Court, Seventh Judicial District, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower - Nixon Political Cartoon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clifford Noble - State Appointment, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee Chairman Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Comptroller Levitt on the Costs of Conforming State Taxes to Federal Provisions, 1961 May 09 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - County Chairman Committee, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - County Chairman Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - County Chairman Correspondence, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - County Chairman Correspondence, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - County Chairman Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - County Chairman Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Department of Mental Hygiene, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower - Campaign Trail, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower Memorabilia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Economy yes - But not as a maker of Policy" - James E. Allen Jr., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Education and Increases by 1960 and 1961 Legislators, 1961 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Election - Canvass of Military Ballots, 1954 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Erie County - Republican County Committee Party Rules and Regulations, 1940; 1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee - Wayne County, 1949-1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Facts about the Hill - Burton Program, 1947 July 1-1965 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Federal Act - Volunteers in Civil Defense Work Oath, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Finger Lake Travel Guides, 1954; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Foundation - Communism, 1958-1959; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Frank C. Moore - Drawing, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Genesee County Republican Committee, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Glyde Central School Cafeteria, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Gross Receipts Tax - Statements, 1950; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Harry C. Bray - Illness, 1950 June (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hospitals - NYS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Inaugural Invitations, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Jefferson County Republican Newsletter, 1947 August (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Joint Legislative Committees, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 40)